

DAVID ANDREW

England born, motivated designer and developer with experience creating custom websites through HTML and CSS. Very strong collaboration skills and proven history of application development. HTML5 and JavaScript, Python and React. Goal-orientated and focused with a drive to succeed. Passionate about building world class websites and applications.

DAVID ANDREW

WEB DEVELOPER GRAPHIC DESIGNER MUSIC PRODUCER (270) 585 0468

Q 40 Jasper Wilson Lane, Russell Springs, Kentucky, 42642

PRO SKILLS

HTML₅

CSS

JavaScript

Python

Github

React

Chrome Dev Tools

Adobe Photoshop

REFERENCE

Vince O'Connor

VOCON Traffic Management - M.D.

T: + 44 3333 448 308 E: info@vocon.co.uk

INTERESTS

Computer Systems Web Development
Astronomy Music Production
Photography Graphic Design
Hiking SCUBA Diving

EXPERIENCE

STOWER

Amazon, Inc/Campbellsville, KY/Jan 2021 - Mar 2021

Responsible for storing merchandise in assorted bin sizes, to be pulled for fulfillment of orders. All items are inspected for damages, then scanned as they are stowed to ensure virtual and physical locations match accuracy of inventory to prevent false overages or true shortages. Speed and accuracy were essential in fulfilling duties and making sure products were available via the website.

TRAFFIC MANAGEMENT OPERATIVE

VOCON Traffic Management/Nottinghamshire, U.K./Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

Duties included installing, maintaining and removal of Temporary Traffic Management equipment such as cones, signs, frames, sandbags and traffic lights on both high and low-speed roads whilst ensuring compliance with the company polocies and the National Highways Sector Scheme. Completion of site maintenance paperwork is also a requirement of this role. Attention to detail is an important, yet necessary skill I continued to develop here.

TRAFFIC MANAGEMENT OPERATIVE

GTM Traffic Management/Nottinghamshire, U.K./Nov 2012 - Mar 2019

Duties included installing, maintaining and removal of Temporary Traffic Management equipment such as cones, signs, frames, sandbags and traffic lights on both high and low-speed roads whilst ensuring compliance with the company polocies and the National Highways Sector Scheme. Completion of site maintenance paperwork is also a requirement of this role. Attention to detail is an important, yet necessary skill I continued to develop here.

EDUCATION

Web Development Course

Commonwealth Coders/Russell Springs, KY/2021 - 2021

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Git, React, Node.js, SQL, Chrome Dev Tools, SASS, MongoDB, JQuery,

General Certificates of Secondary Education

Aston Comprehensive School/Swallownest, Sheffield, U.K./1991 - 1996 English Language, Mathematics, Biology, Physics, Chemistry, Geography, Music, Theater Studies